https://www.universitylanguage.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy for University Language Services
Call Toll Free: 1-800-419-4601
Intl. Call:
1-212-766-3920
Get your FREE Quote Now!
Where to Go
Year, Semester, or Summer?
Where to Go
Year, Semester, or Summer?
HomePrivacy Policy
University Language Services respects your privacy and security. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise share your personal information, such as name, email address, physical address, phone numbers, buying history, etc. without your permission.
At any time you may contact University Language Services with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the personal data you have given us and request correction or deletion. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes.
How We Protect Your Information
Your access to some services and content is password protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. University Language Service will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. You should not disclose your user name and password to others.
FREE Translation Quote in 3 Easy Steps!
1. Contact InformationName: * Company Name: Email Address: * †(privacy policy) Phone Number: * Your Country:AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBrazilBritish Virgin IslandsBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurmaBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandColombiaComorosCongoCongo Dem. Rep. ofCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFiji IslandsFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (North)Korea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotte IslandMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Marianas IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunion IslandRomaniaRussiaRwandaSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychelles RepublicSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSpainSri LankaSt. HelenaSt. Kitts/NevisSt. LuciaSt. Pierre and MiquelonSt. Vincent and GrenadinesSudanSurinameSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin IslandsWake IslandWallis and Futuna IslandsYemenZambiaZimbabweHow did you hear about us?: (Please Select One) Google Search Bing Search Yahoo! Search Other Search College/University Referral Evaluation Service Referral from a Friend or Colleague I am a Previous Customer Other
* Required Fields
2.Project DetailsWhat Service(s) Do You Need?TranslationInterpretingTranscriptionVoice Over ServicesSubtitlingAdvertisingLocalizationGraphic/Web Design
Source Language (From): *Select All that ApplyAfarAfrikaansAkanAlbanianAmharicArabicAramaicArmenianAshantiAymar·AzerbaijaniBafutBahasaBambaraBasqueBassaBelarussianBembaBengaliBislamaBlackfootBosnianBretonBulgarianBurmeseCajunCambodianCantoneseCatalanCebuanoChamoroChichewaChineseChinookCreoleCroatianCrowCzechDanishDariDhivehiDutchDzongkhaEdoEnglishEstonianEweFaroeseFarsiFijianFijian HindiFilipinoFinnishFlemishFrenchFrisianFulaniFuuta JalonGaGaelicGalicianGeorgianGermanGikuyuGreekGreenlandicGuaranÌGujaratiHausaHawaiianHebrewHindiHmongHungarianIboIcelandicIlocanoIlonggoIndonesianItalianJapaneseJolaKannadaKarenKazakhKhalkha MongolKhmerKinyarwandaKirghizKirundiKissiKiswahiliKoniaguiKonoKoreanKurdishKwanyamaKyrgyzLaotianLatinLatvianLiberianLingalaLithuanianLuxemburgianMacedonianMalagasyMalayMalayalamMalinkeMalteseMandarinMandingoMandinkaMaoriMarathiMarshalleseMirandeseMoldovanMongolianNauruanNavajoNdebeleNepaliNiueanNorwegianNzemaOriyaOromoOssetianOtetelaPalauanPapiamentoPashtuPolishPolynesianPortugueseProvencalPunjabiPushtuQuechuaRomanianRussianSamoanSanskritScotsSerbianSesothoSign LanguageSign Language - AmericanSindhiSinhalaSinhaleseSiouxSlovakSlovenianSomaliSoninkeSpanishSrananSwahiliSwatiSwedishTagalogTaiwaneseTajikTamilTeluguTetumThaiTibetanTigrignaTokelauanTonganTurkishTurkmanTuvaluanTwiTzotzilUkrainianUrduUzbekValencianVietnameseVlaamsWallisianWelshWolofXhosaYanomamiYiddishYorubaZarmaZulu Target Language (To): Select All that ApplyAfarAfrikaansAkanAlbanianAmharicArabicAramaicArmenianAshantiAymar·AzerbaijaniBafutBahasaBambaraBasqueBassaBelarussianBembaBengaliBislamaBlackfootBosnianBretonBulgarianBurmeseCajunCambodianCantoneseCatalanCebuanoChamoroChichewaChineseChinookCreoleCroatianCrowCzechDanishDariDhivehiDutchDzongkhaEdoEnglishEstonianEweFaroeseFarsiFijianFijian HindiFilipinoFinnishFlemishFrenchFrisianFulaniFuuta JalonGaGaelicGalicianGeorgianGermanGikuyuGreekGreenlandicGuaranÌGujaratiHausaHawaiianHebrewHindiHmongHungarianIboIcelandicIlocanoIlonggoIndonesianItalianJapaneseJolaKannadaKarenKazakhKhalkha MongolKhmerKinyarwandaKirghizKirundiKissiKiswahiliKoniaguiKonoKoreanKurdishKwanyamaKyrgyzLaotianLatinLatvianLiberianLingalaLithuanianLuxemburgianMacedonianMalagasyMalayMalayalamMalinkeMalteseMandarinMandingoMandinkaMaoriMarathiMarshalleseMirandeseMoldovanMongolianNauruanNavajoNdebeleNepaliNiueanNorwegianNzemaOriyaOromoOssetianOtetelaPalauanPapiamentoPashtuPolishPolynesianPortugueseProvencalPunjabiPushtuQuechuaRomanianRussianSamoanSanskritScotsSerbianSesothoSign LanguageSign Language - AmericanSindhiSinhalaSinhaleseSiouxSlovakSlovenianSomaliSoninkeSpanishSrananSwahiliSwatiSwedishTagalogTaiwaneseTajikTamilTeluguTetumThaiTibetanTigrignaTokelauanTonganTurkishTurkmanTuvaluanTwiTzotzilUkrainianUrduUzbekValencianVietnameseVlaamsWallisianWelshWolofXhosaYanomamiYiddishYorubaZarmaZulu
When is your Translated Document Needed?
(mm/dd/yyyy)
3. Files and Notes†* Attach as many as 7 digital files.
*If you have more than 7 files or files that exceed 5MB each, we will provide you with password-protected access for uploading to our FTP site.
Attach
Also, you can email the files to us directly at service@universitylanguage.com.
Notes & Other Requirements:
Please wait for all file attachments to complete before submitting quote.
Recent Posts
Time Management Tips for College Students
Oct 01, 2020
Ways to Stay Calm When Writing Your First College Paper
Sep 22, 2020
Your Guide to College Video Conferencing
Sep 15, 2020
3 Things to Know About Cybersecurity When Working from Home
Contact Info
15 Maiden Lane, Suite 300 New York, NY 10038 USA1-800-419-4601Int'l Call: 1-212-766-3920Fax: 1-866-662-8048service@universitylanguage.comhttps://www.universitylanguage.com/
Copyright © 1998-2020 University Language Services.
All Rights Reserved.
